

Senior Analyst seeking roles in Software Development, Application
Programming, System Analysis, Technical Architecture, Web Development, Project
Management, Requirement Gathering, HTML, CSS, Python, Hibernate, Javascript



Current Designation: Senior Analyst Total Experience: 6 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Wells Fargo Notice Period: 2 Months

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [computer science

engineering]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore
Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Senior Analyst, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, System

Analysis, Technical Architecture, Web Development, Project Management, Requirement

Gathering, HTML, CSS, Python, Hibernate, Javascript

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

Around 6 years of work experience in Software Development & Maintenance.

Having good knowledge on Java, JSP, Servlets and Oracle SQL.

Expertise in writing queries and making changes in backend. Having experience in writing complex queries and having adequate knowledge on PL/SQL

Knowledge on Requirements Analysis, Design, Impact Analysis and Test Plan Documents.

Experience in MVC architecture.

Having knowledge on HTML, CSS, Jquery, Bootstrap

Having adequate knowledge on developing Spring boot application

Having basic knowledge of Python

Have completed ITIL beginner level certification

Work Experience

Wells Fargo as Senior Analyst

Feb 2017 to Till Date

Working on SQL, J2EE applications as L3 support analyst

Infosys Limited as System Engineer

Jun 2014 to Jan 2017

Project Name : IPM+ Infosys Internal Application

Role: L3 support and development Duration: June 2015 - Till date

Description:

IPM+ is an internal application used by all employees of Infosys. It is a project management tool used to maintain the data of projects which includes project client details, resource allocation details, tools and language used in the project on regular basis.

Responsibilities: Servicing L3 tickets Database modifications Minor enhancements on Java source code Documentation of the application artifacts

Project Name : BNSF

Module Name : Web application Development

Role : System Engineer
Duration : Oct 2014 - Apr 2015

Description:

BNSF (Burlington Northern Sante Fe) railway corporation.

BNSF is the second largest freight railroad network in North America that provides high speed links between western and eastern states.

I have 3months project onboard experience. Have also worked on COC application (Code of Conduct) for BNSF employees.

Roles and Responsibilities:

Code changes, preparing requirements analysis, impact analysis and unit test plan documents.

Testing for issues due to code changes .

JavaScript and DB changes: Worked on a new requirement which required changes to be made in the web application by obtaining data from the database by using MVC architecture.

Adequate knowledge on JSP, servlets.

Adequate knowledge on Oracle stored procedure.

Good knowledge on manual testing.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (computer science engineering) from Visveswaraiah Technological University (VTU) in 2014

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version L	Last Used	Experience
MS Word, Excel, Outlook, Powerpoint			
Eclipse Ganymede, Oracle 10 G			
Java, J2ee, Spring boot, hibernate			
SQL, HTML, CSS, Javascript,Python			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time